https://www.celprogen.com/cms.php?page_alias=privacy-policy

Created with Sketch.
Created with Sketch.
Fixed Leukocytes
Immunoglobulins Depleted Serum (IgG)
Devices
Human Serum Albumin (HSA)
Tissue Culture Media
Colony Forming Unit (CFU)
Cells
Extracellular Matrix (ECM)
Media
Patient-Derived Xenografts [PDX]
Fixed Leukocytes
Immunoglobulins Depleted Serum (IgG)
Devices
Human Serum Albumin (HSA)
All Complete Media With Serum
Colony Forming (CF)
Extra Cellular Matrix
Freezing Media
Serum Free Media
All Serum Free Media
Colony Forming (CF)
All Animal Cell Culture
Canis Familaris (Dog)
All Canis Familaris (Dog)
All Tissue Culture Media
Colony Forming Unit (CFU)
Cells
Extracellular Matrix (ECM)
Media
Patient-Derived Xenografts [PDX]
Resources
Cell Culture F.A.Q.
Media and Matrix F.A.Q.
Cell based Assay (ELISA)
Privacy Policy
Welcome to Celprogen.com (and permutation webpages that provide a direct link to this Privacy Policy – collectively the “Site”), which is owned and operated by Celprogen Corporation (“Celprogen” or “we”). This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about Celprogen’s collection, use, and dissemination practices regarding information that you provide to Celprogen through this Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data use, collection or dissemination practices, such as data collected offline or through websites other than the Site.The Site provides an opportunity for Celprogen investors, prospective employees, and other adults to learn more about Celprogen. The Site is particularly geared to our customer base – biotechnology researchers, pharmaceutical and life science scientists – and to providing them with content, products, and services geared to their industry, to the role they play in their organizations, and to helping them accomplish biological procedures faster, more reliably, and in a cost-efficient manner.Your use of this Site is subject to this Privacy Policy, which you may at any time print or download (or request a printed copy by contacting us as specified below). Whenever you submit information to Celprogen through the Site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Celprogen reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised policy at this location, but such changes will not affect information provided by you prior to the effective date of the change unless you consent otherwise. Please check back for updates to the Privacy Policy.How we collect information about you:When you register with Celprogen via this Site, you will be asked to provide basic contact information (e.g., name, organization, address, phone number, e-mail address, fax number, and so on). On this Site, for example, we may collect and retain contact and other information from you in a number of ways, such as when you place an order, request e-mail updates or other information, complete customer surveys, submit a feedback or contact form, or provide a resume. If any third parties provide information to us about you, we may combine that information with other information we have about you, and if and to the extent we do, we will treat such combined information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.This Site collects various information from you in the course of your navigation of the Site, such as the URL of the site you just came from, the browser version you use, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, IP ports, date/time, size of data transferred, pages you visit, and other “clickstream” data. We are typically not able to relate such data to you as an individual if you merely browse our Site and do not disclose your identity to us, e.g., in connection with a registration. Celprogen also uses "cookies" to enhance your Site visit. A “cookie” is information either temporarily or permanently stored in a file on your computer. You can set your internet browser to reject cookies (refer to your internet browser instructions if you wish to do so), but that may limit your use of some convenience features at this Site.How we use information about you: Celprogen uses information collected by clickstream data collection and cookies to store your preferences, improve web site navigation, make personalized features and other services available to you, compile and analyze aggregate statistics and trends, and otherwise help administer and improve the Site. Where you provide registration information, cookies can also be used to identify you when you log onto the Site or portions of the Site.Except as otherwise stated, Celprogen may use information it collects from you and others to respond to your request, improve the content, services, and products that Celprogen provides, customize this Site to your preferences, communicate information to you (where you have not expressed a preference otherwise), for our marketing and research analysis, and for other purposes identified to you. Some marketing and research analysis is conducted by third parties providing data collection and analysis services under contract with Celprogen, utilizing anonymous data collected from cookies. As noted above, you can reject such cookies by following your browser’s instructions. Celprogen reserves the right to make full use of information that is not in personally identifiable form.From time to time, Celprogen uses contact information obtained via this Site to send e-mail and postal mail supplying customers with the most recent product and service information. If you order products or services via our Site, Celprogen may contact you by e-mail to send you information about your order (e.g., order confirmations, shipment notifications, etc.). Celprogen may also contact Site visitors via e-mail regarding their account status, and about changes to any relevant agreements or policies.In connection with our Rewards Program and /or other promotions, we use the information you submit to maintain your account, measure the benefits for our business and pursue other legitimate business purposes as described in this Privacy Policy and in the terms and conditions (where applicable) for the program or promotion.How information may be disclosed and how it is protected:Celprogen does not provide the personally identifiable information you supply to us to outside mailing lists. Celprogen may share information about you with Celprogens affiliates, successors, and agents/representatives (for example, consultants), which are required to treat the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Celprogen takes reasonable steps to safeguard the information you provide to us. For example, all web pages transmitting personal or financial information are encrypted from your client PC to our servers (which are located in the United States to the extent data on Canadian registered website visitors is concerned) using the standard known as SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). Beyond the SSL barrier your data is protected once it reaches our network through the use of secure firewalls. Portions of your data may also be encrypted on our storage server for additional security. We may disclose personally identifiable information that you provide via this site to respond to law enforcement requests or where required by applicable laws, regulations, or court orders. Furthermore, we may disclose information provided by you in connection with corporate restructuring, sale or assignment of assets, merger, divestiture, and other changes of control or financial status, in which case we will require the recipient to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Because no system is 100% secure or error-free despite taking commercially reasonable steps, Celprogen and its affiliates do not promise, and you should not expect, that information you provide to Celprogen shall remain private under all circumstances. It is your responsibility to safeguard any passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features associated with your use of the Site.Opting out:If you do not wish to receive certain communications from Celprogen, or our affiliates or representatives, you may opt out by: (1) declining the service offered when registering or at other information collection points on the Site, or (2) informing us that you no longer wish to receive such communications. We will comply with such requests unless such communications are required by law or do not require your consent under applicable laws. If you opt out of certain communications, you may not be able to access certain Celprogen products or services. If you would like to opt-out of receiving communications from affiliates or other third parties with whom we shared data in accordance with this policy, please contact such third parties directly.Access to information you provide:You may at any time request access to a summary of your personal information held by Celprogen, and request corrections or updates to that information. Celprogen will make reasonable efforts to respond promptly to such requests, but reserves the right to limit such requests to two per year per individual. Further, our response to such requests may be limited to information under our direct control.Other web sites:This Site contains links to the web sites of other organizations. Celprogen is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites, and unless otherwise specified, does not imply any relationship, sponsorship, or affiliation between Celprogen and these linked sites, or adoption or approval of the content of such sites.How to contact us:For any requests or questions related to this Privacy Policy, or if you have concerns about how information you provide to Celprogen is being used, please contact us at the following address: info@celprogen.com.This Privacy Policy is effective June 12, 2007.
×
